BENJAMIN DI GIORGIO

E: bendigiorgio@gmail.com

P: 08094347288

A: Shimo-Ori, 8160952

LINKS

- · www.bendigiorgio.com
- www.maisondigiorgio.com
- https://github.com/bendigiorgio

| PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages from Rust to Python and Typescript. Specializing in React (Next.Js) applications, however also has experience with building backends in Python. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities.

WORK HISTORY

Maison Di Giorgio - Founder /CEO

Fukuoka, Japan • 03/2022 - Current

- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Coordinated efficient large-scale software deployments.
- Created highly scalable backends which suit clients' needs and keep their side as simple as possible.
- Analyzed existing software implementations to identify areas requiring improvement.
- Promoted brand identity by creating company logos and delivering attractive, user-friendly and unique website.
- Translated customer requirements into technical site concepts for bidding and initial planning purposes.
- Enhanced functionality and appearance of website and repaired functionality issues.
- Designed highly engaging interactive user interfaces that complied with modern web standards.

Hotel Nikko Fukuoka - Hall Staff

Fukuoka, Japan • 05/2022 - 03/2023

- Managed stock and ordering supplies for our continued service.
- Adapted to the number of guests to manage and minimize food loss while ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Translated the complete menu of our restaurant and other restaurants' menus within the hotel from Japanese to English
- Managed correspondence with English speaking guests, in person and via email.
- Coordinated activities and events to create safe, positive

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Next.js
- Typescript Proficiency
- SQL Proficiency
- Data Analysis
- HTML & CSS Expertise
- Production Work
- Web Application Deployment
- User Experience Design (UX)
- Adobe Creative Suite & Figma
- Japanese
- Verbal & Written Communication

EDUCATION

Deakin University

Victoria, Australia • Expected in 10/2023

Bachelor of Marketing: Marketing

Ivanhoe Grammar School

Victoria, Australia • 11/2017

High School Diploma

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google Analytics Professional Certificate
- Food Preparation/Handling Specialty (外 食業特定技能1号技能測定試験)
- JLPT (Japanese Language Proficiency)

- and inclusive environment.
- Mentored and coached new employees to foster positive relationships and encourage successful academic achievement.
- Executed efficient breakfast bar set-up and operations beginning at early hours and finishing prior to check out times.

Italian Basil - Head Chef

Fukuoka, Japan • 11/2020 - 04/2022

- Created online solution for sale of fresh vegetables and consumer goods we produced.
- Created and organized staff rosters.
- Maintained high food quality standards by checking delivery contents to verify product quality and quantity.
- Developed kitchen staff through training, disciplinary action, and performance reviews.
- Placed orders to restock items before supplies ran out.

WEGO - Retail Sales Associate

Fukuoka, Japan • 12/2019 - 04/2021

 Offered each customer top-notch, personal service to boost sales and customer satisfaction.

| TENNIS, FASHION, MUSIC

Tennis has been a passion of mine which I have recently been able to rekindle. I like to keep up my exercise and it is a great way to mix focusing on yourself and improving your game (singles) and also your teamwork and to meet new people (doubles). I constantly want to improve and I find myself always trying to think of ways in which I can.

Fashion has also been a great inspiration in my life and I find myself using bits and pieces of it in my design. Many theories of design overlap including some of the the ratios in fashion (1:1.68 / 3:5 / etc) are also very useful in website design to create balance and to visually flow well. I am a fan of many different brands with some notable ones being: Kidill, Yohji Yamamoto, Maison Margiela and Undercover.

Music has always been an integral part of my life and I will listen to just about anything. I work best with music playing and can match my rhythm to the music. Some of my favorite artists include: midwxst, JPEGMAFIA, ZillaKami and KSHMR.

LANGUAGES

English: Native language

Japanese: C2

Proficient